Thank you for watching!
Thanks again for all your hard work!
Hello! This time we have Nanami Kubota from Ocha-no-Ma and
and Natsumi Nakayama from Ocha-no-Ma!
We will be presenting you with these two, so please stay with us until the end.
Thank you very much!
Now that it's April, many of you may have started a new life, so I'd like to introduce Nanami Kubota.
Nanami Kubota, what kind of new life have you started?
Well, I graduated from high school in March.
Congratulations!
I'm going to continue my studies from April, so I'll do my best to balance my studies and my idol activities.
I will do my best to balance my studies and my idol activities.
This year will be my last year as a high school student, so I want to enjoy my last JK life to the fullest.
I want to make a lot of memories and have a wonderful year.
Let's enjoy the whole year!
And we, Ochanoma, are going to participate in Hello Project Hina Fest 2023 held last weekend.
We participated in "Think Carbon Neutral 2023"!
Yay!
At this year's Hinafes, Morning Musume。' 23 and we, Ochanoma, were able to give a premium performance.
I really learned a lot and I think we were able to absorb a lot of things.
Yes, I think so.
And in May, we will be holding the Ochanoma Concert Tour 2023 Spring Growin' Up!
Yay!
How do you feel about this second concert tour, Kubo and Nanami?
Well, I will do my best so that everyone can see how much we have grown since the first tour.
I'll do my best to show you how much I've grown since the first tour.
First of all, please take a look at this video.
Please take a look.
by H.
I wanted to fall in love, I longed to fall in love, I fell in love, but
But he's more like a big brother than a boyfriend, and he treats me like a child.
But I still told him things. I told him things. I told him far away.
I saw him once a day, called him once a day.
Six months have passed since I realized...
I feel like it's almost like he's my boyfriend.
I love you. You lute me, you hold my hand, you start me off.
He took me by the hand, started me off... and scolded me a lot for being in the industry, but it felt good.
Hey, I love you. You eat well, you have great posture, and you're an okay gal.
I love that she eats well, has a high posture, and is an okay gal.
I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, yeah.
I love you. I love you.
I love you.
Pulled me by the hand
He held me in his arms
Even though I regret it.
I'm sorry I did it.
He scolded me so hard.
I love you.
You're a good eater.
And your hands are really high.
And you've got a little bit of wiggle room.
Some days you look at me like you're not interested in me.
Some days you look like you don't care about me.
But still...
I love it. I love it. I love it.
Yeah!
[Applause]
Are you having fun? Watch the rest of the show!
This is Halo with Nanami Kubota and Natsumi Nakayama from Ochanoma! Stay!
From here, I'd like to talk a little bit about each other.
I'm going to ask you a few questions, so don't think too much and answer them quickly.
Yes, I do.
Natsumi Nakayama says she likes to read fashion magazines.
A one-piece dress.
You will appear as a guest speaker at the Tokyo Women's Pro Wrestling Grand Princess!
How did you prepare for the event?
See a lot of CIA Department
What would you like to improve in 2023?
Her singing and appearance
What is your latest makeup obsession?
Applying eye shadow entirely by hand.
This year marks the 25th anniversary of Hello Project.
Berryz KOBO's "Diary in the Name of the One I Love.
Thank you very much.
There are many things I'm interested in.
You said that your hands are the main focus of your makeup these days.
May I ask what you mean by that?
Lately, I've been applying all my eyeshadow by hand.
I used to apply them carefully one by one with a brush.
I used to apply eye shadows one by one with a brush, but I found that applying eye shadows by hand gives me a better gradation
And it's quicker, so I'm into applying by hand.
I've recently become addicted to applying eyeshadow by hand.
I'm going to try it too.
Please give it a try!
Hello Project is celebrating its 25th anniversary this year, and the song that can be said to be Natsumi Nakayama's starting point is
Berryz KOBO's "Diary of a Loved One".
What do you think?
This song was the first song I performed in a performance test I participated in.
I was in the 6th grade of elementary school at the time.
I brought my school bag that I used to use in real life.
I was in the 6th grade of elementary school at the time, so I brought my real school bag and performed it on stage.
I think it was the song that really started me off.
I would like to see you sing it again someday.
Yes, I would like to see you sing it again someday.
Questions for Kubo and Nanomi will be asked after the VTR.
Hallo! STE!
BEYOOOOONDS new single Seek me, you traveler of destiny April 12 onsion
I have now the night sky that cannot be defiled
BEYOOOOONDS New Single Yomeshinai Yozora wa Yume no Dakunai Yozora ni
April 12 On Scion
Which one? If it's common sense, it's this way.
Or is it the other way around? Come on, tell me.
You've got to love it, you know.
You don't owe me anything.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry...
New Album
Big Love
Now on sale
Oh, I forgot.
How was it?
Yes, it was good.
We added one more song, and it was the last song we performed on stage,
I think we were able to put a lot of our thoughts and feelings into our performance and words,
I think it was such a live performance that we could put a lot of our feelings into both performance and words.
It was a lot of fun.
Uma!
Thank you very much.
The setlist also seemed like we sang songs from our indie days in a flash,
I thought it was a great opportunity to show the history of the band,
It was a lot of fun.
It was fun.
I feel a sense of accomplishment now,
I have a great sense of accomplishment now,
It was great that we could all perform together.
It was great.
I thought we were performing for the last time as a group of 12 just now,
It was really like that, all done in one moment,
I thought that every moment was filled with so many memories.
Congratulations on being alive.
Thank you very much.
From tomorrow, we will go our separate ways,
I will ask you to do your best not to lose.
Let's do our best.
That's all for Smileage.
Thank you very much.
Hallo! Sta.
Next, I would like to ask Nanami Kubota a question.
Yes, I would like to ask her a question.
Okay, here we go.
I would like to ask you what kind of hair cut you would like to try in the future. What kind of hairstyle would you like to try in the future?
A pink haircut.
What are you currently doing to achieve your dream?
Sleeping.
If you could produce an event or program produced by Nanami Kubota, what would it be?
An event filled with cuteness.
What is the cutest item you have recently acquired?
A pink phone case.
What song from Hello! Project's history would you like to perform in front of an audience?
Berryz KOBO's "I'm in a relationship but I have a one-sided love.
Thank you.Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
So, I would like to ask you something that has been on my mind,
If you were to produce an event or program produced by Nanami Kubota, what kind of event would it be?
What kind of event would that event be?
Yes, that's right. First of all, I would decorate the room with pink and lace,
Everyone will be dressed in pretty, pink, frilly clothes,
Men and women alike will wear them,
Everyone will be saying "Kururun" together,
I would like to have an event filled with cuteness and fun.
I'd like to see it once.
Really? Then please wear it. By all means.
I'll definitely go.
I would like to ask you about another cute item you recently got, a phone case.
Yes. It's pink and has my favorite anime character on it.
I got the phone case, but my phone case has been broken for a long time,
I didn't have a chance to buy one, and now I'm really happy that I finally did.
Thank you very much.
So, Hallo! Ste will continue after this.
This is Nanami Kubota from Tea Horse!
I'm here at Hello Kitchen.
I'm not a very good cook.
I cook only a few times a year.
I'm a bit nervous about it.
I've been wanting to be a part of Hello Kitchen for a long time.
I've always wanted to be a part of Hello Kitchen.
So I'm very happy to be here.
I'll do my best.
I look forward to working with you today.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
What are you making today?
Pasta with bacon and mushrooms in tomato sauce.
I'll do my best.
It's simple.
I think it's rare to make tomato sauce from scratch.
I hope you will learn how to make it.
I'll do my best.
Let's do our best!
I look forward to working with you.
Now, let's start making the tomato sauce.
Canned tomatoes.
I'm talking whole tomatoes, you know, the kind with the whole tomatoes in them.
Onions and carrots.
That's all there is to tomato sauce.
And olive oil.
It looks so simple.
It's very simple,
If you cut them like this, you can peel them by hand.
I understand.
I haven't used a knife in a very long time.
Slowly.
How much should I cut?
With a pop.
I see. This way?
Yes, that's right.
Ah.
That's what I meant.
Is that correct?
Yes, it is.
You should lower this side.
Lower.
That's right.
Yes.
Can you put it in?
Yes, you can.
Yes, I can.
I'll take care of it first, so take your time.
Cut well.
Then take it out with your hands.
Use the back of the bottle to crush the bottle like this.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's already here, isn't it?
It smells so much garlic.
It smells delicious.
Do you like garlic?
I love garlic.
Yay.
I'll get you one more, okay?
What?
Well, a little bit.
I'm going to cook it slowly in olive oil.
I'm thinking there are about 4 servings.
I want to transfer the flavor of the garlic to the olive oil.
I like to watch cooking. I also like to eat it.
I watch cooking shows and think it looks delicious. I feel like I'm making it.
But you don't actually cook much? No, I don't. I make mistakes.
I make mistakes. If I make it alone, like for Valentine's Day, it explodes.
I tried to make it bigger and put it in the microwave, but it exploded and smelled burnt.
Chocolate? I gave up after three failures that day.
Chocolate? You should have told me earlier. I would have done the batteries.
They started to seethe right away, so I put them on very low heat.
It's out of the oil, so I asked him to put it inside.
Can you turn it over and take care of it? I'll take care of it.
Looks delicious. It smells good, doesn't it? It smells so good.
My favorite food is garlic shrimp.
How do you eat it? Rice and garlic shrimps.
It goes well with rice. I think it would be good with bread, too.
I like garlic toast very much.
You like garlic. I hate it! You are not a cute girl, are you?
Her voice suddenly became high pitched. It's fine. A girl who likes garlic.
You're going to burn my precious garlic.
It's not that it's burning, it's just that it looks good.
Take this and put it in here.
The others are still a little more.
Put the little ones in here.
This is the important part. If you don't keep them at this level, they will become bitter.
They become bitter? Anyway, keep the heat low.
When you think it's not good, cut it off and let it cook slowly.
Saute the onions in olive oil with a delicious garlic aroma.
I'll put them in like this.
I'll put them in like this, and once they've reached this point, they're ready to go.
Oh, I see.
Before today.
Yes, yes.
Ahead.
Yeah.
Oh no! I'm tearing up!
From the bottom to the top.
Can you cut it pretty sharply?
Yes, it does.
If it's a very sharp cut, it means that the way I cut it wasn't very good.
What! Really?
I think it wasn't cut very well.
There's a grinding sound.
Oh, that's not good?
Yes. That's why the fibers are crushed, and the tangled lines are coming right here.
Cut this off, too.
It's usually cut.
Yes, that's good.
That's good, isn't it?
Start with medium heat, medium or low? Medium heat.
Slowly turn it into a candy-like color.
Candy brown?
Like a fox color.
Oh, like candy canes.
Yes, yes, yes.
But is there such a thing as candy? Nowadays.
I once made Beckomen as a science experiment.
Isn't that amazing?
But it's that color.
I see.
It turns brown and transparent.
It becomes clear and fragrant.
I see.
It takes quite a long time.
There is a key point. If you put a little salt on it, you can pick it up and make it flutter.
Ah!
Flip, flip, flip, flip. Ah! Yes, yes, yes.
Ha-ha-ha. It was a dream that I finally, finally got it.Ha-ha-ha. It was a dream that I finally got it.
I had dropped this in the same place. Oh, I'm sorry.
I see.
The onions were a little tense earlier, weren't they? If you don't make the onions sweet, the pasta sauce won't be rich, so I used tomato sauce.
I like onions. Onions and garlic are also onions, aren't they?
Oh, yes. My favorite food when I was little was leeks. Green onions?
Oh no, all I said was something not so cute. Oh no.
When I went to an udon restaurant and they offered all-you-can-eat green onion, I'd just say, "Gabbaa!
When I brought them to the table, they said, "She likes green onions, doesn't she? Oh, she did.
Yes, I became friends with the person sitting next to me.
Ah, that's good, isn't it? Negi communication.
Yes, that's good. Say you like him.
That was a good way to put it, wasn't it? Indeed.
It's a bit mocking, isn't it? Yay!
I'm the cutest girl in the group.
I guess. Cute?
Yes, I'm cute. Yay! I'm so happy!
But you know what? That's a bit of an aim, isn't it?
Yes, people say that's not good, but I'm not really aiming for it.
It just happens. That's right. I have a cute face, so it's just the way I am.
Maybe that's true. That's right.
She's amazing. The way she looks at the camera.
You are always conscious of it. Yes, I am. They are always taking pictures of me.
Be delicious. Be delicious.
It's this way toward that way. Oh, I'm sorry.
Be delicious. Yes. Make it delicious.
But it's getting clearer and clearer.
Not quite there yet. It's still about 20%.
I'm getting a little tired. I guess so.
Shall we leave it alone for a while? Yes.
If you leave it alone, only the bottom part of the screen will be dark,
You can move it once in a while.
It's difficult because it's so weak. Looks delicious.
Is it heavy?
No, it's not heavy. I didn't do it on purpose. This might be really heavy.
I can't wait to see what happens next.
Yes, it is. Yes, it is. I might have been struggling a lot right now,
I think the dish will be very perfect in the end,
I hope you are looking forward to it.
I hope you are looking forward to it. I am looking forward to it.
The teacher was very easy to talk to,
He lets me taste the food a lot,
That's for sure.
That made me very happy.
I did my best in cooking like this,
How about you, Natsumi Nakayama?
I am not a good cook,
Recently, I made pot-au-feu,
I am addicted to making pot-au-feu on a hot plate,
I'm into making pot-au-feu on a hot plate, and I try my best to keep it warm with lots of vegetables.
I would like to try it someday.
Please come and try it.
Hello! Project 25th Anniversary
My name is Kuriho Kamiko from Angelem.
This year marks the 25th anniversary of Hello! Project is celebrating its 25th anniversary this year,
Project has a long, long history,
Thanks to that history, we are here today.
Hello! Project, and it is thanks to that history that we are able to be active in the Hello!
I would like to do my best so that we can continue to build on this history.
I would like to introduce a music video that I would like to recommend.
The theme is expressive and energetic.
I would like to introduce Morning Musume。 I'm here!
Please have a look.
Nyururi1Distribution
Thank you for watching our video!
It will continue again!
Rot through hell!
You ask me what I want to do, but
You'd be surprised what I'll tell you.
When I start talking about something you don't know
But when I start to tell you something you don't know
We're still in the middle of our dreams
We're all in the middle of a dream
No excuses Goodbye Bye Bye
There's a chance for you
Hero game
Play Through, Break Yourself Down
The song is full of energy and each member's expression is really rich and full of energy.
Hallo! Sta.
Next is the presentation of the lyrics that touched my heart.
Project has many wonderful lyrics,
Project, but I was impressed by Berryz KOBO's and ℃-ute's "Amazuppai Haru ni Sakura Sakurano Nakano" ("From Among the Cherry Blossoms in Sweet and Sour Spring").
I thought the lyrics "Sweet and sour spring, dream shining" by Berryz KOBO and ℃-ute were very good,
I thought the lyrics were very good, and I thought that when spring comes, everyone is running toward their dreams,
I thought the lyrics were very good,
I thought it was very good.
I thought the lyrics were very good.
I, Nakayama, was a member of "℃-ute" and I was a member of "You ride a bicycle, I ride a train and go home.
I am Nakayama, a member of ℃-ute, and I am going home by train.
The phrase is "You ride a bicycle, I ride a train home,
I am from Ishikawa Prefecture, where it snows in winter.
I can't ride a bike in winter because of the snow,
But as spring approaches and the snow melts, I can ride my bike home.
I love this phrase because it reminds me of a scene where the snow melts and I can ride my bike home.
I love it very much.
It's wonderful.
Now please watch the VTR.
Please watch the VTR.
The presentation of the lyrics that touched my heart. In this corner, we will present the lyrics of the songs of Hello!
Project's songs and talk about their charms. Project songs and talk about their charms. This time, I, Sakura Ishiyama, will make a presentation. This way, please.
Even if it's a roundabout way, it's okay if you get there, if you smile at the end, today is more important than tomorrow.
It's a song by Angerme called "Nanitenbi hachifuke" (Seven falls, eight falls),
I think everyone has passed through this path at least once or twice when they are trying to achieve a goal and feel like running away from it,
When you listen to this song at such times, it gives you a boost and pushes you forward, just as the song says, "If you smile at the end of the day, you'll have a smile at the end of the day,
I have been listening to this song since I was a trainee.
I tend to take everything too seriously and think too much, or I tend to think that I have to move forward only looking ahead,
I tend to think that I have to just look forward and move on, but with the various members of the group, I can go down a different path with them,
There are many members who give me things other than what I think,
But as a result, I have a lot of fun and can always laugh,
This is one of the situations where I think it is good to be a part of a group,
I think that is what the lyrics of the song are about.
When I think about it too much, I sometimes become hardened,
I often think about it and become hardened,
Or if I smile at the end of the song, or if today is more important than tomorrow,
How do you say it? It's like they're telling me that I'll be fine,
The lyrics make me feel more at ease, so I think it's really good.
It's like the lyrics "Today is more important than tomorrow,
I have a tendency to dwell on what I will do tomorrow or what I will do if I make a mistake in the future,
I have a tendency to get stuck in my thoughts about what to do tomorrow or what to do if I make a mistake in the future,
Listening to this song made me think that I should cherish the present moment and live with energy and vigor.
So, that was the lyrics presentation that touched my heart.
Hello! STE!
With Nanami Kubota of Ochanouma,
Natsune Nakayama of Ochanouma, and the members of Halo! STE, presented by Nanami Kubota of Ochanouma and Natsune Nakayama.
It is time for us to say goodbye.
Here is an announcement.
On May 10th, Ochanouma First Rise Tour 202Cherry blossoms bloom beyond the cold
Brightly clad in light
The white stuffed grass softly tells me
Please think of me
Last year's broken love
Even goodbyes are treasures
Now my heart is calling me
I want to believe in you
Habiniki Guy, take off your boots
Take me away, take me away, take me away
Red penicure, deliver my love
The more the spring market is, the more real it is
I want to hold you in my arms
I want to hold you in my arms, I want to hold you in my arms, I want to hold you in my arms
Shining new world, let's go out for love
I want to hold you in my arms
Every time our eyes meet I know what you wish for
I want you to be closer to me than anyone else
I want you to touch me, you're all I have
Let's change our clothes for spring, let's put the past behind us
Spinning the past, I expose my true self
White nekorte, pure heart to devote
I can't disappear as long as there's a spring market
Make it your own, my budding feelings
feelings, the pain that thrills me
I'm melting into you, melting into you
Melting snow in a new world, let's start a love affair
Words, music, arrangement by Makoto Yamaguchi
Song: Yamaguchi, Makoto
Drawings Yamaguchi Makoto
Movie Makoto Yamaguchi
Video Yamaguchi Makoto
Picture Makoto Yamaguchi
Video Makoto Yamaguchi
undefined